<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[dinais.me]]></title>
  <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-31T18:04:07+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dina]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Friend]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/best-friend/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-31T18:01:01+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/best-friend</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello best friend, ironic ain&rsquo;t it? I called a site as best friend, but that&rsquo;s what I feel. I can&rsquo;t share if I am not feeling fine with my family in Indo, otherwise they will be very worried, but if I share stuff with my family here they don&rsquo;t believe me.</p>

<p>Now what hurts most is, when you tell someone you are not feeling fine, they&rsquo;d say, it&rsquo;s only on your head.</p>

<p>I try to believe that they are right, so live my days as they go. Bye.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[It obviously comes when it's colder?]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/it-obviously-comes-when-its-colder/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-23T17:55:56+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/it-obviously-comes-when-its-colder</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yeah two days ago, it was 18-23°c here in Germany, it was spring!</p>

<p>But since yesterday, the temperature dropped dramatically until 5°.</p>

<p>I got headache again :&ndash;( Though it was gone after I took Tomapiring but it is the same headache, the same location..</p>

<p>Plus I felt strange in my chest, sooooo tired feeling again..</p>

<p>So let&rsquo;s hope it&rsquo;s temporary..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nicee.....]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/nicee-dot-dot-dot/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-18T21:35:35+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/nicee-dot-dot-dot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s just soooooooooooo nice to live our days when we are healthy. I am happy :-D</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feel Sooo Tired]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/feel-sooo-tired/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-13T14:12:45+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/feel-sooo-tired</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I don&rsquo;t know what&rsquo;s wrong with me, I feel so tired in the afternoon, after doing literally nothing.</p>

<p>Morning, taking my little darling to Kindergarten, go home, cleaning the house a bit not the hard tasks, pick her up again, prepare lunch, eat our lunch, clean the dishes, and now hardly can do anything because of tired feeling.</p>

<p>I want to check, but will they believe me? It was a Brain Tumor suspicion and now Heart disease suspicion, they&rsquo;ll think I am crazy, making it up.</p>

<p>But no, I don&rsquo;t, I feel there is something wrong with me.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life is Just Amazing - Be Happy]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/life-is-just-amazing-be-happy/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-09T23:25:54+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/life-is-just-amazing-be-happy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When you wake up, sun shines, bird sings, you are feeling HEALTHY, what else do you want? This is my life when I have no headache or just the sign of it.</p>

<p>Happily grilling and having a meal with my family, I want nothing else.</p>

<p>Yeah, it may nothing to some, but to be healthy and be with my family is everything to me. As simple as that. G&#8217;night.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Days No Headache - Endings]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/two-days-no-headache-endings/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-08T19:09:23+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/two-days-no-headache-endings</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since I got two worst headache two or three days ago, I didn&rsquo;t even feel something on my head in the last two days, it was a bliss.</p>

<p>However, today, I felt slightly terrible headache for a few seconds infront of computer.</p>

<p>I did neck-gym 20 times, seems to be better, but I don&rsquo;t want to have this kind of headache again, please not this one..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Comes After Meals]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/it-comes-after-meals/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-06T07:13:18+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/it-comes-after-meals</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This two worst headaches that happened yesterday, I noticed it always came after meals. The first one came right after lunch, I was even still on my dinning chair.</p>

<p>The second one happened right after my dinner.</p>

<p>Sounds hard to believe but this headache is the one that happened in summer last year, when I called my mom in law to come over.</p>

<p>God, I hope it won&rsquo;t come again&hellip;</p>

<p>It sounds crazy, but I told my husband to sue my first doc if it is a BT.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worst Headache of Mine]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/worst-headache-of-mine/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-05T13:53:29+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/worst-headache-of-mine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While I am having lunch today, I have worst headache ever, it was like 5-6 seconds on my forehead, but when it happened, It hurt so much that I would fall down on my chair.</p>

<p>I hope it would be the last time, because I&rsquo;ve been well and happy in the last days.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headache-Free Day]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/headache-free-day/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-02T18:42:12+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/headache-free-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First day ever, I don&rsquo;t feel strange feeling &ldquo;ache&rdquo; in my head. So nice!</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s just amazing how to feel healthy, simply no pain.</p>

<p>Happiest day of my life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Day With Tomapirin]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/another-day-with-tomapirin/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-28T14:15:14+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/another-day-with-tomapirin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is a little bit cold, it can be the snow that we had yesterday, more and less 5 degrees.</p>

<p>Strange enough, because it&rsquo;s colder today, I don&rsquo;t have strange feeling on my chest or heart, but I do have terrible headache right after I picked my little darling from Kindergarten.</p>

<p>So bad that I took another Tomapirin and thanks God, it is now gone.</p>

<p>But I really wonder when does thing like this end in my life?</p>

<p>Anyway, here is the pic I took from a hill behind our garden, it was beautiful and make me smile seeing this scenery.</p>

<p><img src="http://ingoditrust.github.io/images/2014/02/white-hill-feb282014.JPG" width="300" height="150" title="white snow hill" alt="white snow hill"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Weird Morning]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/another-weird-morning/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-26T10:30:48+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/another-weird-morning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This morning, like yesterday, I got my feet hurt like crazy, and feeling weird while making my own breakfast, felt like I would pass out, but I didn&rsquo;t.</p>

<p>When I went to Kindi with my little darling, talked with another mom, she said, she feels the same, unwell, and want to pass out.</p>

<p>It could be the weather, which seems really crazy at the moment, yesterday was so warm, today is a little bit cold, etc.</p>

<p>Sigh, I wasn&rsquo;t like this, also the age huh..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Doc Appointment]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/new-doc-appointment/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-25T10:28:11+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/new-doc-appointment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, another Doc&rsquo;s appointment is done, though I doubt if I had to make it.</p>

<p>I am so glad that today I felt really well, slightly headache but not bad, but still wondered what it was yesterday.</p>

<p>Yesterday, my feet hurt like crazy, and both of them, and I felt something weird inside my chest. Can be heart failure sign, but my God, how pathetic I feel now, but it was something wrong, I felt VERY tired right in the morning immediately after I woke up, which was weird.</p>

<p>I got enought sleep, but weird both feet ache, and weird feeling in my heart or chest.</p>

<p>Before calling the doc, I thought, &ldquo;will he believe what I will say or share to him what I am feeling or have been feeling?&rdquo;</p>

<p>Because the doc will be my new &ldquo;HausArzt&rdquo; and I was in doubt if this doc will actually listen.</p>

<p>I need someone who can &ldquo;listen&rdquo; to me.</p>

<p>So appointment will be on March 10th.</p>

<p>Oh I went to shop, which is now a great stuff to do with this condition :(</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tired After Baking One Cake?]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/tired-after-baking-one-cake/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-22T21:26:40+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/tired-after-baking-one-cake</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I think I&rsquo;ve never felt THAT tired today, I was questioning myself, what have I done?</p>

<p>I just baked one cake yesterday, and I am dead tired today, couldn&rsquo;t even pick the cake&rsquo;s plate up from Kindergarten kitchen.</p>

<p>It was once happened, I felt so tired but I forced myself to shop as I thought, I wasn&rsquo;t going to die just because I feel tired.</p>

<p>But in the shop, I felt like I would fall. If I don&rsquo;t have kids I would risk it. But my young kids need me, so I follow what my body says today, &ldquo;don&rsquo;t go&rdquo;.</p>

<p>I just can&rsquo;t believe that I am feeling so very tired just because baking ONE cake. Not normal afterall.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scratchy Head]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/scratchy-head/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-22T20:11:54+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/scratchy-head</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My Phsychotherapist once told me, when I comb my hair, I should pull my hair out gently, and I do it too.</p>

<p>However, I sometimes feel like I have ants on my head, and it feels scratchy.</p>

<p>I often look myself at the mirror and focusing on my head skin if there is a blood shed or something like that because I scratched them often. But it didn&rsquo;t then what it is?</p>

<p>I want to know what I am fighting..but it aint easy when you&rsquo;re alone..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just One Tomapirin Today - Bliss]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/just-one-tomapirin-today-bliss/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T19:10:56+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/just-one-tomapirin-today-bliss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Couldn&rsquo;t help it this morning, took Tomapirin and it helped. Baked the cake, finished it as I have to bring it there tomorrow morning, and felt the headache.</p>

<p>Attempted to take another Tomapirin, but thank God, it was gone all of sudden.</p>

<p>I don&rsquo;t feel it right now, but I have the Radiologie CD result from the doc.</p>

<p>Still hoping it won&rsquo;t be something to worry about.</p>

<p>Good night.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insecure world writable dir]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/insecure-world-writable-dir/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T17:05:24+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/insecure-world-writable-dir</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Answer: chmod go-w /thedirectory/</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing my New Git]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/testing-my-new-git/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T16:41:07+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/testing-my-new-git</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Let&rsquo;s see if this works. Not much in front of it though.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insomnia or Just Stuffed Head]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/insomnia-or-just-stuffed-head/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T04:28:23+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/insomnia-or-just-stuffed-head</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>04:28 I was awake since 03:00, as always I was thinking right after I was awake, do I have headache now?, I didn&rsquo;t.</p>

<p>But like now when I am in front of my terminal, I have a slightly headache, I am thinking, it&rsquo;s my closed nose. Nothing to be worried about.</p>

<p>Then after an hour trying to sleep, I failed miserably.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s friday, will be a sort of hectic day, still going to bake a cake for &ldquo;Kindi börse&rdquo; for tomorrow.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s just the result of tugging my little darling in bed early &ndash; result of this insomnia or full-stuffed head.</p>

<p>Yeah, they will ask me, why are you too worried? you have healthy kids (which is true, and I am so thankful for) and loving husband..</p>

<p>When I am asked like this, I wish they knew how to be in my shoes. Good night/morning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Must Hello World]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/a-must-hello-world/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-20T19:16:06+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/a-must-hello-world</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Another hello world post, if you&rsquo;re listening.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
