<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Dinais.me]]></title>
  <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-25T10:33:18+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dina]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Doc Appointment]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/new-doc-appointment/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-25T10:28:11+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/new-doc-appointment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, another Doc&rsquo;s appointment is done, though I doubt if I had to make it.</p>

<p>I am so glad that today I felt really well, slightly headache but not bad, but still wondered what it was yesterday.</p>

<p>Yesterday, my feet hurt like crazy, and both of them, and I felt something weird inside my chest. Can be heart failure sign, but my God, how pathetic I feel now, but it was something wrong, I felt VERY tired right in the morning immediately after I woke up, which was weird.</p>

<p>I got enought sleep, but weird both feet ache, and weird feeling in my heart or chest.</p>

<p>Before calling the doc, I thought, &ldquo;will he believe what I will say or share to him what I am feeling or have been feeling?&rdquo;</p>

<p>Because the doc will be my new &ldquo;HausArzt&rdquo; and I was in doubt if this doc will actually listen.</p>

<p>I need someone who can &ldquo;listen&rdquo; to me.</p>

<p>So appointment will be on March 10th.</p>

<p>Oh I went to shop, which is now a great stuff to do with this condition :(</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tired After Baking One Cake?]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/tired-after-baking-one-cake/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-22T21:26:40+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/tired-after-baking-one-cake</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I think I&rsquo;ve never felt THAT tired today, I was questioning myself, what have I done?</p>

<p>I just baked one cake yesterday, and I am dead tired today, couldn&rsquo;t even pick the cake&rsquo;s plate up from Kindergarten kitchen.</p>

<p>It was once happened, I felt so tired but I forced myself to shop as I thought, I wasn&rsquo;t going to die just because I feel tired.</p>

<p>But in the shop, I felt like I would fall. If I don&rsquo;t have kids I would risk it. But my young kids need me, so I follow what my body says today, &ldquo;don&rsquo;t go&rdquo;.</p>

<p>I just can&rsquo;t believe that I am feeling so very tired just because baking ONE cake. Not normal afterall.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scratchy Head]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/scratchy-head/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-22T20:11:54+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/scratchy-head</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My Phsychotherapist once told me, when I comb my hair, I should pull my hair out gently, and I do it too.</p>

<p>However, I sometimes feel like I have ants on my head, and it feels scratchy.</p>

<p>I often look myself at the mirror and focusing on my head skin if there is a blood shed or something like that because I scratched them often. But it didn&rsquo;t then what it is?</p>

<p>I want to know what I am fighting..but it aint easy when you&rsquo;re alone..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just One Tomapirin Today - Bliss]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/just-one-tomapirin-today-bliss/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T19:10:56+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/just-one-tomapirin-today-bliss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Couldn&rsquo;t help it this morning, took Tomapirin and it helped. Baked the cake, finished it as I have to bring it there tomorrow morning, and felt the headache.</p>

<p>Attempted to take another Tomapirin, but thank God, it was gone all of sudden.</p>

<p>I don&rsquo;t feel it right now, but I have the Radiologie CD result from the doc.</p>

<p>Still hoping it won&rsquo;t be something to worry about.</p>

<p>Good night.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insecure world writable dir]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/insecure-world-writable-dir/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T17:05:24+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/insecure-world-writable-dir</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Answer: chmod go-w /thedirectory/</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing my New Git]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/testing-my-new-git/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T16:41:07+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/testing-my-new-git</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Let&rsquo;s see if this works. Not much in front of it though.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insomnia or Just Stuffed Head]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/insomnia-or-just-stuffed-head/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-21T04:28:23+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/insomnia-or-just-stuffed-head</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>04:28 I was awake since 03:00, as always I was thinking right after I was awake, do I have headache now?, I didn&rsquo;t.</p>

<p>But like now when I am in front of my terminal, I have a slightly headache, I am thinking, it&rsquo;s my closed nose. Nothing to be worried about.</p>

<p>Then after an hour trying to sleep, I failed miserably.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s friday, will be a sort of hectic day, still going to bake a cake for &ldquo;Kindi börse&rdquo; for tomorrow.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s just the result of tugging my little darling in bed early &ndash; result of this insomnia or full-stuffed head.</p>

<p>Yeah, they will ask me, why are you too worried? you have healthy kids (which is true, and I am so thankful for) and loving husband..</p>

<p>When I am asked like this, I wish they knew how to be in my shoes. Good night/morning.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Must Hello World]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/a-must-hello-world/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-20T19:16:06+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/a-must-hello-world</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Another hello world post, if you&rsquo;re listening.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
