<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Rants | dinais.me]]></title>
  <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/categories/rants/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-09T23:27:56+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dina]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Days No Headache - Endings]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/two-days-no-headache-endings/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-08T19:09:23+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/two-days-no-headache-endings</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since I got two worst headache two or three days ago, I didn&rsquo;t even feel something on my head in the last two days, it was a bliss.</p>

<p>However, today, I felt slightly terrible headache for a few seconds infront of computer.</p>

<p>I did neck-gym 20 times, seems to be better, but I don&rsquo;t want to have this kind of headache again, please not this one..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Comes After Meals]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/it-comes-after-meals/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-06T07:13:18+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/it-comes-after-meals</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This two worst headaches that happened yesterday, I noticed it always came after meals. The first one came right after lunch, I was even still on my dinning chair.</p>

<p>The second one happened right after my dinner.</p>

<p>Sounds hard to believe but this headache is the one that happened in summer last year, when I called my mom in law to come over.</p>

<p>God, I hope it won&rsquo;t come again&hellip;</p>

<p>It sounds crazy, but I told my husband to sue my first doc if it is a BT.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worst Headache of Mine]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/worst-headache-of-mine/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-05T13:53:29+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/worst-headache-of-mine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While I am having lunch today, I have worst headache ever, it was like 5-6 seconds on my forehead, but when it happened, It hurt so much that I would fall down on my chair.</p>

<p>I hope it would be the last time, because I&rsquo;ve been well and happy in the last days.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Day With Tomapirin]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/another-day-with-tomapirin/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-28T14:15:14+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/another-day-with-tomapirin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is a little bit cold, it can be the snow that we had yesterday, more and less 5 degrees.</p>

<p>Strange enough, because it&rsquo;s colder today, I don&rsquo;t have strange feeling on my chest or heart, but I do have terrible headache right after I picked my little darling from Kindergarten.</p>

<p>So bad that I took another Tomapirin and thanks God, it is now gone.</p>

<p>But I really wonder when does thing like this end in my life?</p>

<p>Anyway, here is the pic I took from a hill behind our garden, it was beautiful and make me smile seeing this scenery.</p>

<p><img src="/images/2014/02/white-hill-feb282014.JPG" width="300" height="150" title="&lsquo;white snow hill&rsquo; &lsquo;white snow hill&rsquo;" ></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tired After Baking One Cake?]]></title>
    <link href="http://ingoditrust.github.io/tired-after-baking-one-cake/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-22T21:26:40+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://ingoditrust.github.io/tired-after-baking-one-cake</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I think I&rsquo;ve never felt THAT tired today, I was questioning myself, what have I done?</p>

<p>I just baked one cake yesterday, and I am dead tired today, couldn&rsquo;t even pick the cake&rsquo;s plate up from Kindergarten kitchen.</p>

<p>It was once happened, I felt so tired but I forced myself to shop as I thought, I wasn&rsquo;t going to die just because I feel tired.</p>

<p>But in the shop, I felt like I would fall. If I don&rsquo;t have kids I would risk it. But my young kids need me, so I follow what my body says today, &ldquo;don&rsquo;t go&rdquo;.</p>

<p>I just can&rsquo;t believe that I am feeling so very tired just because baking ONE cake. Not normal afterall.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
